=== UPM - User PDF Manager ===
Contributors: SparkTech , Towhidul, Raiyan , Mostakim 
Tags: PDF Manager , User PDF Secured
Requires at least: 6.7
Tested up to: 6.7
Stable tag: 0.1
Requires PHP: 8.2
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

The UPM - User PDF Manager plugin allows admin to assign pdfs for each authorized user. Get started now!

== Description ==

UPM - User PDF Manager plugin is an official plugin maintained by the WordPress team that allows administrators to assign pdfs for each authorized user and display them on the website. A user is only be able to see the pdfs which is assigned to him.

UPM - User PDF Manager is an official WordPress plugin, and will be fully supported and maintained until 2026, or as long as is necessary.

At a glance, this plugin adds the following:

* Administrators can create custom posts under the User PDFs section and assign pdfs for each user.
* Administrators can add 'Id Number' of the pdfs for each user.
* Administrators can add 'Full Name' of the user for each user.
* Administrators can add 'Registration Number' of the pdfs for each user.
* Administrators can add 'Start Date & Time' of the pdfs for each user.
* Administrators can add 'End Date & Time' of the pdfs for each user.
* Administrators can add the policy status of the post.
* When policy status is 'Active' the pdfs will be displayed to the respective user.
* When policy status is 'Expired' the pdf will be hidden from the user.
* The pdfs can be displayed and viewed from the website through the shortcode [user_pdfs].

== Changelog ==

= 0.1 =
Initial release.

== Installation ==

1. Upload the `upm-user-pdf-manager` folder to the `/wp-content/plugins/` directory.
2. Activate the plugin through the 'Plugins' menu in WordPress.
3. Add new post for each user to assign pdfs from User PDFs menu in admin panel. 
3. Use the shortcode `[user_pdfs]` to display PDFs assigned to users.

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

= How can I assign a PDF to a user? =
Navigate to the 'User PDFs' section in the admin panel, create a new post, and assign upto 10 PDF to the user.

= Can users see PDFs assigned to other users? =
No, users can only view PDFs assigned to their accounts.

= Contact the support =
If you are still experiencing issues after trying these steps, you can contact the UPM- User PDF Manager Support team at mostakim.bdcalling@com for assistance.



